thinkresult.in 2016-06-23

# Think Result - Fast Growing Digital Media Network - CPM, CPC, CPL, Video, Mobile

**We are deeply committed to protecting the privacy of Internet users.**

Please read this privacy policy before using the site or submitting any personal information. We strictly adhere to all industry guidelines, and will continue to review and improve our privacy policy and procedures to ensure the safety and protection of consumer information. By using the site, you are accepting the practices described in this privacy policy.You are encouraged to review the privacy policy whenever you visit the site to make sure that you understand how any personal information you provide will be used. 

B D Digital is one of the digital media network platform enabling advertisers and marketers across the region to communicate with their audiences and helping publishers to grow their revenues with better optimization and campaign planning. We are headquartered in the Nashik, India. We provide this privacy policy (“Privacy Policy”) so that we may inform you about how our ad optimization technology, including our Ad Network Platform for online advertisers including Real-Time Bidding Service (collectively, the “Service”) gathers and processes information on behalf of (i) advertisers, agencies and ad networks, and any other media-buying clients (collectively “Demand Partners”); and (ii) website owners, mobile application owners, ad networks, ad exchanges, sell-side platforms and any other suppliers of advertising inventory for sale (collectively “Supply Partners”); wherein Demand Partners and Supply Partners in (i) and (ii) above together are “Clients”.

B D Digital products and services are designed to help Demand Partners optimize deliveries and ROI on their ad campaigns and help Supply Partners maximize revenue earned on every impression. Advt.creative that you see come from these Demand Partners and usually the ad comes from our/third party ad server running, or from the same domain as the Demand Partner or the Supply Partner. Generally, a user will encounter an ad from one of our demand partners by viewing the content on a website& mobile applications owned or operated by one of our Supply Partners.

**A GENERAL NOTE ON INTERNET TECHNOLOGIES AND PRIVACY**

Ad Tags: Ad Tags are pieces of code that allow the delivery of online advertisements in the dedicated ad spaces on websites and in online applications. Our Ad Tags may transmit certain anonymous information about the web site, section of the site and size of the ad that we are optimizing.

API: An application programming interface or “API” is a particular set of rules and specifications that allows one software program to access and make use of another software program. It helps facilitate the interaction between applications, similar to the way the user interface facilitates interaction between humans and computers. We use API to make a bid request on RTB inventory sold by Supply Partners. 

Cookies: Cookies are small text files that web servers typically send to users’ computer when they visit a website. Cookies can be read or edited when the user loads a website or advertisement from the domain that wrote the cookie in the first place. Cookies are used by companies to collect and send information about a user’s website visit – for example, number of visits, average time spent, pages viewed, navigation history through the website, and other statistics. This information can be used to improve a user’s online experience by saving passwords, or allowing companies to track and improve website loading times, for instance. Cookies can also be used to track a user’s browsing or online purchasing habits and to target advertisements to specific users. Users who prefer not to accept cookies can set their Internet browser to notify them when they receive a cookie or to prevent cookies from being placed on their hard drive. You can read more about cookies at http://www.allaboutcookies.org/cookies/. 

Personally Identifiable Information: We define personally identifiable information (or “PII”) as “information that can be used to uniquely identify, contact, or locate a single person or can be used with other sources to uniquely identify a single individual.” e. g. name, address, e-mail address etc. This is the common industry definition used by most Internet companies. Information that is collected by various Internet companies but which does not qualify as PII is call “non-PII.” 

Real-Time Bidding: Real-Time Bidding (or “RTB”) is a method of buying online or mobile advertising inventory by responding in real-time to an ad call with a “bid,” usually priced by cost per thousand impressions (“CPM”), to buy that single impression and thus the opportunity to display an ad to that user. RTB buyers use multiple different data sources, including third parties, to more precisely target the ads they display. 

Web Beacons & Pixels: A web beacon consists of a small string of code that represents a graphic image request on a web page, a page in an online application, or in an email. A graphic image can be associated with the web beacon, but is not required. When an image is present, usually the image is designed to blend into the background of the web page, application, or email in which it appears. Often a beacon will be placed by an online data collecting company without an image, so it is invisible to the user, and in the smallest discrete space possible on the screen. This is a “pixel” and is essentially an invisible web beacon. Pixels and web beacons can be used for site traffic reporting, unique visitor counts, advertising auditing and reporting, personalization, and other uses. They do this typically by writing or editing cookies on each user’s computer. Therefore, like cookies, they cannot be used to key log, copy personal files from your computer, or replicate like a virus. Most pixels and web beacons, including those used by us, collect only anonymous data. However, some may be used to collect PII, particularly in the case of email that contains a web beacon. In such cases, the data collected through the web beacon may be linked to the recipient’s email address or other information identifying the recipient. 

**B D Digital - SERVICE & THE DATA IT COLLECTS **

We may or may notcollect personally Identifiable Information. B D Digital uses one or more third party ad serving technology to serve ads at this site and at our clients’ sites. In the course of delivering an ad to you, the third party ad serving party may place or recognize a unique cookie on your browser and use information about your visits to this and other Web sites in order to provide advertisements about goods and services that may be of interest to you. We may collect personally identifiable information, like names, postal addresses, email addresses, etc., when voluntarily submitted by our visitors. This information is only used to fulfill your specific request, unless you give us permission to use it in another manner. 

**Cookies**   
“Cookies” are strings of text that a web site transmits to a user’s computer. Cookies enable a website to keep track of a user’s preferences and activities relating to that website. Our website creates a temporary cookie for each visit in order to facilitate the visit. These cookies automatically expire as soon as you leave our website.   
The World Privacy Forum has published an article on cookie opt-out. If you would like to read more about this, please visit this link: htttp://www.worldprivacyforum.org/cookieoptout.html. You may follow the procedure laid out in the said website to opt out of Cookie. 

**Third Party Cookies**  
In the course of serving advertisements to this site, our third-party advertiser may place or recognize a unique “cookie” on your browser. 

**Distribution of Information**   
we may share information with governmental agencies or other companies assisting us in fraud prevention or investigation. 

**Commitment to Data Security**  
Your personally identifiable information is kept secure. Only authorized employees, agents and contractors (who have agreed to keep information secure and confidential) have access to this information. All emails and newsletters from this site allow you to opt out of further mailings. 

**Industry Efforts to Protect Consumer Privacy**  
We are committed to protecting the privacy of Internet users. Accordingly, we strictly adhere to all industry guidelines, including those established by the Direct Marketing Association 

**Consumer Choice – Opting Out of Receiving Cookies**

We use technology which includes cookies and web beacons in the delivery of our Services.  
We believe that the use of these tools enables us to provide users with a more meaningful web experience. 

You may adjust your computer’s web browser settings to refuse all cookies.However, please note that because cookies are widely used, disabling the use of cookies in your web browser may interfere with full use of various websites. 

You may opt out of receiving cookies by clicking here:¬¬¬¬¬¬¬¬¬¬________________________ 

“Opting Out”through The Network Advertising Initiative 

You can also opt out of receiving cookies from some third party and any other Network Advertising Initiative (NAI) compliant company by clicking here:http://www.networkadvertising.org/managing/opt_out.asp. 

You will find a mechanism to opt-out from Non-PII collection by a number of different Demand Partners and other Internet companies, including third-party data providers. If you opt-out through the NAI, please refer to the FAQ (http://www.networkadvertising.org/managing/faqs.asp) available on the NAI website to understand how their opt-out mechanism. 

**InformationSecurity**

We follow generally accepted industry standards to protect against unauthorized access to, destruction or disclosure of data. This includes undertaking necessary physical, electronic and management activities required to protect data integrity, access and use. Any data that is stored on our/ third party servers is treated as confidential and is not made generally available to the public. 

Our servers are protected by firewalls and are located in secure data facilities to further increase security. Please keep in mind, however, that despite these reasonable efforts to protect data on our servers no method of transmission over the Internet is guaranteed to be secure. 

Therefore, while we strive to protect your personal data or information at all times, we cannot guarantee its absolute security and shall not be liable for any breach of security by an outside party.
